FIRST LETS UNDERSTAND WHAT THESE VARIABLES SAYS:

Admission to a degree program represents a challenge for new students, which those that show
greater emotional stability and ability to face college adjustment will best solve. The assessments are to better understand a person's strengths and weaknesses, identify problems with cognitions, emotional reactivity, and make recommendations for treatment/remediation.
This psychometric assessment is based upon College Adjustment Scale (CAS).
It is a rapid method of screening college students for common developmental psychological problems.